你发现时他们就这样了吗
You found them like this?
我来看凯伦...
I came to see Karen...
发现了地上的血迹
and I saw the blood on the floor.
然后闻到了气味
Then I smelled them.
有人把他们拖到这里
Somebody dragged them out here
然后放火焚烧
and set them on fire.
他们杀了他们  然后放火焚烧
They killed them and set them on fire!
你是个警察
You're a cop.
你查清楚是谁干的  然后把他们交给我
You find out who did this and you bring 'em to me.
听懂了吗  把他们交给我
You understand? You bring 'em to me.
我们会查出是谁...
We'll find out who--
-我需要重复吗  -不用
- I need to say it again? - No. No.
我知道你的感受  我也经历过
I know what you're feeling. I've been there.
你见过我的样子  那很危险
You saw me there. It's dangerous.
-凯伦不该被烧死  -对
- Karen didn't deserve this. - No.
大卫不该被烧死
David didn't deserve it.
-谁都不该  -好了  哥们  别...
- Nobody does. - All right, man, let's--
不查出是谁干的  我绝不离开
Man, I ain't going nowhere till I find out who did this!
我们是一边的  哥们
We're on the same side, man.
听着
Hey, look,
我知道你的感受
I know what you're going through.
我们都失去过爱人
We've all lost someone.
我们知道你现在的感受
We know what you're going through right now,
但你得冷静下来
but you've got to calm down.
-你给我退后  -别这样
- You need to step the hell back! - No.
她不会想要你这样的
She wouldn't want you being like this.
住手  住手
Stop! Stop!
住手
Stop!
够了
That's enough.
瑞克
Rick.
-住手  -放开我
- Stop. - Let go of me!
-不  -放开我
- No. No. - Let go of me!
不
No.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译  冰蓝
翻译  33来了
翻译  Reginamoon
翻译  重案组李Sir
翻译  卫老哥
翻译  Eowyn
翻译  送小饭
翻译/校对  送小孩
翻译/校对  爱卿遛小鸟
校对  冰蓝  米小勒
时间轴  加森  雪贵人
时间轴  marktaotao
特效/后期  、青衣
特效/后期  吉吉
总监  Lemony  送小孩
行尸走肉
第四季  第三集
你的伤至少得一周才能痊愈
This is gonna be sprained at least a week.
好消息是  这些伤口都无需缝针
Good news, none of these cuts need stitches.
接下来的几天不要打字
I wouldn't plan on much typing the next few days.
你没事吧
You okay?
很痛
It hurts.
我说的不是你的手
I wasn't talking about the hand.
我们刚经历了可怕的事
We just went through something terrible.
那些我们竭力阻止的事情
Everything we've been working so hard to keep out,
终究还是发生了
it found its way in.
不
No.
该发生的总会发生的
It's always there.
明早要开委员会
Council meeting tomorrow morning.
通知你一声
Thought you should know.
我们失去了12名同胞
We just lost 12 of our own.
还有两名被无情杀害
Two more we killed in cold blood.
疫情恐怕难以控制
We could be facing an outbreak.
仅仅一天  我就闯了不少祸
I think I've done enough damage for one day.
我以前也失控过
I've fallen off the wagon before.
-是一回事吗  -差不多
- That's what this is? - Pretty close.
当遇到问题  我不会唉声叹气
When it happened, I didn't stand around feeling bad about it.
我会挺住
I got back up.
我会担起责任
I had responsibilities.
保护大家的安全
People to keep safe.
老兄  去清洗下伤口吧
Let's get you cleaned up, man.
说不定要缝上几针
You might even need a couple stitches.
先把他们安葬了再说
Not until they're in the ground.
那你至少得让赫谢尔或者斯蒂文斯医生看看
You should at least let Hershel or Dr. S. take a look at you,
确保没什么大碍
make sure nothing's broken.
先把他们安葬了再说
When they're in the ground.
我不会有事的  对吧
I'm gonna be okay, though, right?
你看凯伦和大卫都已经被感染了
I mean, Karen and David, they were already sick.
所以要感染的话  这会儿早就被感染了
So if we were gonna get it, we'd have had it by now.
又没有固定的发病时间
It doesn't happen on a timeline.
这是因人而异的
It's different with everyone.
但我们会没事的
But we could be okay.
对  会没事的
Yeah, we could be.
一切都会好起来的
Everything could be okay.
如果是跟行尸  跟活人正面交锋
If it's walkers, if it's people,
我们还有法子  可以拼了
we can do something. We can fight.
但遇上这个  我只能掘坟墓
But with this, I'm just digging graves.
得去找S医生
Got to see Dr. S.
我会没事的
I'm gonna be okay.
S医生
Dr. S....?
医生你在吗
Dr. S.?
我们必须告诉他们
We have to tell them.
感染扩散了
It's starting.
病毒传播很快
It's spread.
D区幸免遇难的人中  萨沙和迦勒已经感染
Everyone who survived the attack in cell block D.
现在其他人也出现了症状
Sasha, Caleb, and now others.
哦  天呐
Oh, Jesus.
那我们该怎么办
So what do we do?
当务之急  封锁A区
First things first. Cell block A is isolation.
像之前萨沙和迦勒那样  将所有被感染的人隔离
We keep the sick people there like we tried with Karen and David.
那接下来又怎样
What the hell we gonna do about that?
让瑞克去调查
Ask Rick to look into it.
做个时间表  记录每个人在何时何地做什么
Try to make a timeline-- who's where when.
但要怎样才能阻止疫情恶化呢
But what are we gonna do to stop this?
没办法阻止
There is no stopping it.
被感染了  就会恶化
You get it, you have to go through it.
-那这不就是等死吗  -病毒本身不致命
- But it just kills you? - The illness doesn't.
是症状要命  我们需要抗生素
The symptoms do. We need antibiotics.
附近的药店我们都去过了
We've been through every pharmacy nearby.
没找到多少
And then some.
西桃工学院的兽医院
That veterinary college at West Peachtree Tech,
应该没人想到
that's one place people
去那里找药
may not have thought to raid for medication.
动物的药  人也能用
The drugs for animals there are the same we need.
距这里有50英里
That's 50 miles.
之前觉得太冒险
Too big a risk before.
现在不管了  我带一组人出去
Ain't now. I'm gonna take a group out.
抓紧时间
Best not waste any more time.
我也去
I'm in.
你没有接触过病毒
You haven't been exposed.
达里尔接触了  你跟他在一辆车里的话
Daryl has. You get in a car with him...
他已经把虱子传给我了
He's already given me fleas.
我可以带路
I can lead the way.
我知道东西放在哪
I know where everything's kept.
在外面的时候  每次都有危险
When we're out there, it's always the same.
早晚得跑步逃命
Sooner or later we run.
那我就给你们画张地图吧
I can draw you a map.
我们应该做一些其他的预防措施
There are other precautions I feel we should take.
比如
Like what?
达里尔这组人
There's no telling how long it'll be
什么时候回来说不准
before Daryl and his group return.
我们应该把最易被感染的人隔离开
Wouldn't it make sense for us to separate the most vulnerable?
我们可以用行政办公楼
We can use the administration building.
有独立的办公室和房间
Separate office, separate room.
谁是最易被感染的人
Who is the most vulnerable?
孩子们
The very young.
老人呢
What about the old?
我来试一下
Give me another go at it.
管子被泥土堵住了
The whole line's mudded up.
那头又掉到池底了
The end is dragging the bottom again.
我们得出去清理一下
We'll have to go out there and clear it.
设好诱饵  从墓地穿过去
Set the bird, go out through the tombs,
再从森林小路绕到后面
swing around through the forest route.
我们现在的水还够用  明天再说
We got enough for now. That's tomorrow's problem.
瑞克  萨沙被隔离之后
Rick, five more people
又有五个人死了
have come down with it since Sasha went in.
我们的人所剩无几
There's not a lot of us left.
要是你我病了怎么办
What if you get sick? What if I do?
我们要是在外面遇险回不来怎么办
What if we get in trouble out there and don't come back?
先把这水给需要的人
Let's get this up to the people who need it.
先把必要的事做好
Let's get what we have to get done first.
卡尔还在为被隔离的事生气吗
Is Carl pretty pissed about going into quarantine?
当然了
Of course.
但还是安全更重要
But it's better to be safe.
安全总是更重要
Always better to be safe.
你应该跟他谈谈
You should talk to him.
我们应该去哀悼一下
We should both pay our respects.
我先解决这个问题  待会儿见
I'll take this up first. Meet you.
对于发生的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about what happened.
我对你做的事情
What I did to you.
所有事
Everything.
我们都有责任
It's on both of us.
你要查出来是谁干的
You got to find who did this.
我不太了解大卫
I didn't know David much.
你呢
Did you?
有人和他或者和凯伦有仇吗
Did anyone have a problem with him or Karen?
不  不可能
No. No way.
我每天都跟她在一起
I was with her all the time, every day.
她跟所有人都相处得很好  大卫也是
She got along with everybody. Same with David.
当时只有他们两个病了
They were the only two who were sick.
做这件事的人可能是想阻止病毒蔓延
The person who did it might have trying to stop this thing from spreading.
他们没成功
They didn't.
如今萨沙也病了
Now Sasha has it.
听着  不管是谁干的
Look, whoever it was who did this,
他们逃不了的  我们会找到他们的
they're not going anywhere. We'll find them.
今天找  现在就找吗
Today? Right now?
因为我没觉得你很紧张这事儿
Because I'm not feeling the urgency.
我只看见你在泵水
All I see you doing is pumping water.
实际上  我的感觉是
In fact, what I'm picking up is
在这里  即便是谋杀也是可以被接受的
murder is okay in this place now.
不  不是的
No, it is not.
但我们得先保命
But we have to save lives first.
我们得维持这个地方的运转
We have to keep this place going.
你去操心那个吧
You worry about that.
我来操心正确的事
I'll worry about what's right.
这是为了你好
It's for your own good.
我很好
I'm fine.
我可不想和群孩子关在一起
I don't want to be locked away with a bunch of kids.
我需要你在那儿照看朱迪思和其他人
I need you in there keeping an eye on Judith and everybody else.
确保他们的安全
Making sure they're safe.
假如有人生病  你得让我知道
If anybody gets sick, you let me know.
若我发现时  他们已经变异了呢
What if they've already turned when I find them?
除非必要  你不能开枪
You don't fire unless you absolutely need to.
但你知道我有可能得开枪的  是吧
But you know I might need to, right?
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
-格伦  -别
- Glenn? - Don't.
-别  别进来  -怎么了
- Don't-- don't come in. - What is it?
我病了
I have it.
他妈的机油不够了
Son of a bitch is about a quart low.
你还是把机油放在三号塔底了吧
You still keep it in the bottom of tower three?
是的
Yeah.
我去拿
I'll go get one.
我很开心你在这儿
I'm glad you're here.
我还能在哪儿
Where else would I be?
四处漂泊
Running off.
你知道我不会再漂泊了
You know I'm not running off.
所以还是像以前那样  只剩我和你了吗
So it's just gonna be me and you like in the old days?
是啊  还有鲍勃
Yeah, and Bob.
但还是缺个人手
Still, feels like we could use another person.
还有谁没病
Who else isn't sick?
我们没问瑞克
We don't ask Rick.
他想留下陪卡尔和小拽女
He wants to stay here with Carl and little ass-kicker.
确保他们安全
Keep them safe.
加上这儿有许多事他可以做
Plus there's plenty of stuff he could do here.
那我们还能找谁
So who else we got?
你在这儿
Oh, there you are.
我费了好大劲儿找你
Took me damn near forever to find you.
你在干嘛
Whatcha doing?
得有人看着  以防奸人图谋不轨
Somebody needs to stand watch.
伙计  我也想找到元凶
Man, I want to find them, too.
为他们干的事射他们一箭
Put a bolt in them for what they did.
这里被封锁了
These people are cut off.
如果有人进出的话
Ain't no way anyone's getting in and out
那么多人不可能没人看见
without a whole bunch of people seeing 'em.
萨沙还在里面  我哪里都不会去
Sasha's in there. I ain't going nowhere.
如果我们不带药回来  那在这里守着也没用
Standing guard ain't gonna do no good unless we come back with them meds.
好吧
All right.
我们在前门加油
We're gassing up by the front gate
改变主意了就来找我们
in case you change your mind.
平静的大海
练    不    出
优秀的水手
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
我在这下面躲开你们
I'm down here away from y'all
因为你们这些孩子应该离我远点
'cause you kids are supposed to stay away from me.
我在巡视走廊
I've been walking the halls.
我爸让我照看大家
My dad told me to look out for everyone.
你应该保持距离
you should keep your distance.
你在往出口走
You're walking towards the exit.
我要出去
I need to go out there.
去牢房吗
To the cell blocks?
去林子里
To the woods.
那你就是在偷偷溜走咯
So you're sneaking out.
我不需要任何人替我操心
Don't need anyone worrying about me
我也不想让别人告诉我能不能去
and I damn sure don't want someone telling me I can't go.
我不允许你独自去林子里
I can't just let you go out into the woods by yourself.
允许我
Let me?
我没法阻止你
I can't stop you.
但我必须告诉我爸
But I have to tell my dad.
那就去吧
Go ahead, then.
等你找到他时我已经在外面了
I'll be out there by the time you find him.
赫谢尔
Hershel.
如果你一定要去
If you have to go,
那我就跟你一起去
then I have to come with you.
卡尔
Carl.
我必须这么做
I have to.
我发誓  这只是过敏
I swear, it's just allergies.
-珍妮特  -很快就会好的
- Jeanette. - They come and go.
-珍妮特  -伍德伯里来的人都知道
- Jeanette. - Ask anyone from Woodbury.
珍妮特
Jeanette.
卡萝尔
Carol...?
米卡说你在这里
Mica said you were here.
我觉得不舒服
I don't feel good.
没事
It's okay.
别担心
Don't worry.
Hey, don't worry.
我们会让你好起来的
We're gonna get you better.
去里面躺着吧
You just go in there and lie down.
你会帮我盖被子吗
Will you tuck me in?
你认识我的朋友格伦吗
You know my friend Glenn?
他是我知道的最会盖被子的人
He's the best tucker I know.
他一定会让你觉得温暖舒适  好吗
And he'll make sure that you feel toasty and warm, okay?
好了  没事的
Okay. It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
会没事的  去吧
It's all right. Go on.
谢谢你肯留在这里
Thanks for being in there.
我知道你不是非得这么做
I know you don't have to be.
但这对朱迪思意义重大
It means a lot you being in there with Judith.
外面还好吗
Things okay out there?
格伦被感染了
Glenn has it.
玛姬
Maggie.
我们不能沮丧
We don't get to be upset.
大家各司其职  爸爸总是这么说
We all got jobs to do. That's what Daddy always says.
达里尔和米琼恩会找到药的
Daryl and Michonne will get the meds.
你和卡萝尔
You and Carol
还有瑞克要在他们回来前照顾大家
and Rick will help everyone till they get back.
我会照顾朱迪思
And I'll take care of Judith.
只需要关注我们该做的事
Just focus on what you have to do.
不论发生什么  我们都能解决
No matter what happens, we'll deal with it.
我们必须解决
We have to.
你爸什么时候把枪还你的
When did your dad give it back?
昨天
Yesterday.
就在那一切发生后
After everything happened.
你过去几个月成长了很多
You've grown a lot these last few months.
你知道要担起责任了
There's a responsibility about you.
让你冷静一段时间看来很有帮助
I think it's done you good to step back.
是啊
Yeah.
还可以
It was all right.
我不能总那样
Can't be like that all the time.
我自己在这里也没问题
I would have been fine on my own.
这里真平静
It's peaceful out here.
过去这几天
These last couple days,
在这墙外说不定比里面更安全
we might be safer outside those walls than in.
才不是呢
No, we're not.
我们走吧
Let's wrap this up.
别
Don't.
你不必这么做的
You don't need to.
刚才这里真是平静
It was so peaceful.
的确
It was.
但也不会总那样
Can't be like that all the time.
没有看起来那么糟
It's not as bad as it looks.
别哭
Don't do that.
好的
Okay.
我的样子肯定很糟
I must be a sight to see.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
-我听说了凯伦的事  -别说了
- I heard about Karen-- - Don't.
现在别想这个
Don't think about that now.
想想努力康复
Think about getting better.
想想积极的事
Positive thoughts.
乐观一点
Positive vibes.
我不知道
I don't know.
达里尔带了一队人出去
Daryl's got a group going out.
他们去找药了
They're getting medicine.
赫谢尔知道个地方
Someplace Hershel knew about.
那个兽医学院吗
That veterinary college?
-那太远了  -但他们很有信心
- It's far. - But they feel sure about it.
说不定明天就有药了
So we could have medicine as early as tomorrow.
我们还有机会
We've got a chance.
-泰  -休息一下
- Ty. - Get some rest.
我得走了
I got to go.
情况还好吗
Everything look all right?
还行
Yeah.
扎克把这车保养得很好
Zack kept this thing running pretty good.
这是扎克的车吗
This is Zack's car?
是啊  我们速度最快的车
Yeah, fastest one we got.
你还好吗
You all right?
你真的希望我陪你去吗
You really want me coming along?
这词怎么念
What's that word?
扎那米韦
"Zanamivir".
一种抗流感药
是啊  我们需要你
Yup, we need you.
-怎么了  -多一个人坐得下吗
- What's up? - Still got room for one more?
没问题
Hell, yeah.
很好
Good.
我去拿装备
Just got to get my gear.
好吧
All right.
天呐  我没看到你在那
Oh, God, I didn't see you there.
很抱歉打扰你
Sorry to interrupt.
没关系
It's okay.
你还好吗
You okay?
我要跟达里尔出去一趟
I'm going on the run with Daryl.
但我想知道
But I was wondering--
我知道有很多人都身处困境
I know there's a lot of people in trouble.
生病了
Sick.
我知道你是什么样的人
It's just I know how you are.
你在乎别人
You care.
谢谢
Thank you.
不知道你能不能帮我照顾萨沙
I was wondering if you could look in on Sasha for me.
有你照顾她  我就放心些
It would make me feel better knowing you were looking in on her.
如果不行的话...
If you can't--
不
No.
我乐意效劳
No, I'd be happy to.
谢谢
Thank you.
凯伦的事  我很遗憾
Oh, what happened to Karen, I'm so sorry.
你怎么不在隔离区
Why aren't you in quarantine?
我在那里对大家都没好处
I'm no good to anyone in there.
爸爸  求你了
Daddy, please.
玛姬  亲爱的  那里有很多人饱受煎熬
Maggie, dear, there are people in there suffering.
我能帮他们退烧  维持性命
I can bring their fever down and keep them stable.
达里尔去拿抗生素了
Daryl's getting the antibiotics.
他们有的人根本撑不过12小时
Some of these people won't last 12 hours.
我不能让你这样做
I can't let you do this.
玛姬  格伦就在里面
Maggie, Glenn's in there.
怎么回事
What's going on?
接骨木
Elderberries.
以前我妻子泡茶总会放这个
My wife used to make tea with them.
这是天然的抗流感药
They're a natural flu remedy.
迦勒病得厉害没法看病  但我可以
Caleb's too sick to help. I can.
我们有太多次对我们身上
There's so many times we haven't been able to do anything
所发生的不幸毫无回天之力
to change what was happening-- what was happening to us.
我们希望可以  事实却不尽如人意
We wished we could, but we couldn't.
但这次  我可以
This time, I can.
我很清楚
I know I can.
所以我必须这么做
So I have to.
赫谢尔  你进去会得病的
Hershel, if you go in there, you're gonna get sick.
等等  我们可不确定
Wait, we don't know that.
我们只知道这些人的病症必须得到控制
What we do know is that these people's symptoms need to be controlled.
赫谢尔  拜托  我们可以等等
Hershel, please. We can wait.
听我说  该死
Listen, damn it!
走出去是在冒生命危险
You step outside, you risk your life.
喝口水是在冒生命危险
You take a drink of water, you risk your life.
如今连呼吸
And nowadays you breathe,
都是在冒生命危险
and you risk your life.
现在我们别无选择
Every moment now you don't have a choice.
能选的只有为什么而冒险
The only thing you can choose is what you're risking it for.
我能让这些人好转一点
Now I can make these people feel better
多撑一阵子
and hang on a little bit longer.
救人一命
I can save lives.
这理由足以让我冒险了
That's reason enough to risk mine.
你们都明白
And you know that.
爸爸
Dad.
玛姬
Maggie?
爸爸走了
Daddy's gone.
他走了
He left.
我知道
I know.
他给你说去哪了吗
Did he tell you where he went?
没有  但是...
No, but...
我知道
I know.
怎么知道的
How?
S医生病了
Dr. S. is sick and...
我们要各司其职
We all got jobs to do.
我们能坚强面对的  对吧
We'll deal with it, right?
我们不能沮丧
We don't get to get upset.
该死
Damn it.
糟了
Shit.
卡萝尔  快跑
Carol! Run!
见鬼
Shit.
快跑
Run!
小菜一碟
Piece of cake.
我们说过明天再干
We decided to do that tomorrow.
都不知道有没有明天
We don't know if we get a tomorrow.
我知道你不会再去漂泊
Hey, I know you weren't running off.
但问题是  我们找不到他了
The thing is, that trail went cold.
你知道的  对吧
You know that, right?
如果找到了
If it was any different,
我会陪你一起去的
I'd be right out there with you.
能给我拿张CD吗
Would you hand me one of them CDs right there?
避难所
Find sanctuary.
是人声吗
Was that a voice?
活下去...
Determined to survive...
活着
Keep alive.
抓稳了
Grab something!
左转
Go to the left.
卡住了
We're jammed up.
往那边的缺口跑
Make a run for the gaps right there.
你们俩朝树林跑
You two, you make a run for the
不要停下  听见了吗
woods and you don't stop for nothing, you hear me?
现在
Now!
跑
Move!
泰
Ty!
快跑
Go! Come on!
来咬我啊
Come on and get me!
你们走
Go! Go!
走吧
Come on.
来啊
Come on and get me!
快走
Go!
快
Come on.
等等
Hold up.
走
Come on.
喝下去
Drink it.
撑住  医生
Hang in there, Doc.
你不该来这里
You shouldn't be here.
换你也会来
Tell me you wouldn't be.
如果你在外面
If you weren't in here already,
也会来的
you'd be in here.
我没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
把这个敷头上
Keep this on your forehead.
兽医医嘱
Veterinarian's orders.
真可恶
This sucks.
经历了那么多
After everything,
我们却被小小的感冒打败了
we just get taken out by a glorified cold.
别那样说
Don't say things like that.
也别那样想
Don't even think things like that.
不说也只是口是心非
All I can do is stop saying them.
不  你可以做到更多
No, you can do more.
我们已经走了这么远
We got this far somehow,
你应该有信心
you can believe somehow.
我们都要各司其职
Now we all have jobs here.
这就是你要做的
That one's yours.
你那样做很蠢
That was a stupid thing you did.
去外面冒险
Going out there like that.
没错
Yes, it was.
你为我们和孩子们
You know, you do a lot for us,
付出很多
for the kids.
你牺牲很大
You sacrifice a lot.
为了我们  你什么都愿意做吗
Is there anything you wouldn't do for the people here?
愿意
No.
卡萝尔
Carol...?
凯伦和大卫是你杀的吗
Did you kill Karen and David?
是的
Yes.